how to get out of it
to do so in less than 20 days
worth JP
I don't know anything
500 brownies to deliver today brother
and then he's giving me a ride
and will also help me
of course
with the recordings
send a lot
3rd point of sale of Charlie Brown animal
we are here
Charlie Brown
she laughed at me
said maybe I was a guy
I remember I was on this street here o
exchanging bigger ideas
trying to sell the brownies
guys wasn't giving me so much morale
and today put it back in the first points of sale
on the main street
Santos gastronomic
hand march
it's victory
is on
you already have
I offer you my Mercedon
Here we GO
I just closed 1 more point of sale
goes from all saints
come hillside baby
our proposal
Charlie Brown
if you want I'll give you 1 period of 5 days
I send it to you
dust can be like this o
too easy
bro let's go
I will give 1 retreat
I will enter the Cora app
and here I enter the New Contact slip
take expiration date
bro what day is today
is on
what day is today
brother excuse in morale
issue ticket
share newsletter
pass me 1 zap
brother in the crowd
caraca where is the story
you man who discredited you
are you seeing
you remind me that I came to bring the brownie
and then beauty
okay packing ready
Charlie Brown
in the houses
but now
the time has come to raise the level
if it works out bro
will be bursting
tiredness for caraca bro comes